A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Soul and I traveled to Italy to collect Kishan souls for an extracurricular lesson.
We were able to meet our quota for the lesson.
But just as we were about to leave, I sensed a troubling soul wavelength nearby.
Something told me that I shouldn't open that door, but I didn't listen.
Inside, we found a soul who had crossed beyond the realm of humanity.
Meister and weapon is one, on the verge of becoming a Kishu.
We tried to fight them, but...
I screwed up.
Kishu
I'll see you next time.
Thank you.
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
やっと理由は途絶びに突きつけられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
ソウル!
ゴーオン クロナ
フィニッシュ
メドゥサ ウィッチ
ウィッチ ウィッチ ウィッチ ウィッチ
Kill them and eat their souls,カロナ
I think I can deal with that
ROAD Skype
Wake up.
Soul, please.
You dumbass.
Hurry.
Get out of here.
Okay.
Soul.
This is all my fault.
What's happening?
How did that get there?
Professor Stein!
If he's here, then that blade must be...
Your papa has arrived.
That's right, Maka.
Take a good look at how brave and selfless your father is.
Professor Stein, is Soul all right?
The wound's very serious.
If we don't get him treatment soon, he might not make it.
He's not even looking at me.
I gotta say, though, it was an easier fight than I expected.
I harden the blood around your wound to stop the bleeding.
Do I get a thank you?
Yeah, thank you.
Thank you very much!
Are you gonna make me hurt you?
Professor Stein?
Hmm?
Who are those two?
Or what are they?
I've never seen anything like this.
That is the reason the Academy was created.
The reason the Academy was created?
So does that mean he's a Kishin?
Technically, not yet.
But he's only one step away from it.
Listen to me, Stein.
Take Death Scythe and find the Demon Sword.
Stop it from awakening into a Kishin.
That is the reason you called me back to the Academy in the first place.
I'll take care of the sword.
We cannot allow the Kishin to be reborn into the world.
Do your job well, Stein.
I'm counting on you.
All right, then.
Let's take care of this, shall we?
Yeah.
Corona, quit standing there staring into space like an idiot.
If you don't get it in gear, we're going back to the sleep deprivation again.
No!
Don't start waking me up every hour again!
I don't like it! The dark circles under my eyes will come back,
and I don't know how to deal with the dark circles!
The Grim Reaper has sent his greatest meister armed with Death Scythe.
This should be a good test to see how long Krona can last.
Krona, get them now!
Spirit, can you stand against the Demon Sword?
Of course I can.
What do you think I am, some kind of rusty old dagger?
Been a long time, hasn't it?
Since we teamed up like this?
We're not as young as we used to be, that's for sure.
Speak for yourself. I haven't aged a bit.
Would you hurry up and attack already, you idiot?
But I've never seen a man with a screw sticking out of his head before!
I don't know how I'm supposed to deal with a guy like that!
You eat him! Swallow his soul!
Soul Force!
Professor hit him with his soul wavelength!
Directly!
This way he might actually be able to do some internal damage!
Ah!
Have another.
What?
That's the blood from the wound we gave him.
Mati Nido!
Professor!
He's using every drop of his blood as a weapon.
But how is that even possible?
When souls are overhunted, a Demon Sword is created.
We have to stop him here and now, or he will definitely become a Kishin.
What's more, the balance of power between these two is uneven.
The weapon's soul is clearly dominant.
It rules over the Meister's more introverted soul, confining it.
For the moment, the Meister still has some strength left to fight back against the weapon.
But if he should be completely swallowed up, things will get dangerous.
There's something else.
I see a snake coiled around him.
What's it doing there?
If you let him hit you with that technique again, I'm gonna stick thumbtacks in your shoes.
Got it?
No!
Thumbtacks in my shoes would stick into my feet whenever I tried to walk.
It would hurt.
I don't think I could deal with that, really.
Look!
Oh, I see.
Professor Stein has a specific fighting style.
First he guards, using my dad only as a shield.
Then he uses his own attack.
Soul force.
Oh, wow.
Damn.
A time-lag attack.
It's time to die, screwhead!
Professor!
I think I'd like to dissect you now.
Pee-yah!
Screw yourself!
You won't live that long!
You ready?
Yep.
We actually need them!
Spirit run.
Oh, dear!
I think this is too much for me!
Let's see you stop all of these!
Where did the screwhead freak go?
I don't see him!
Where the hell is he?
Dammit!
He scrambled what little brains you have left!
Hurry up and snap out of it!
We can't afford another hit from his soul wavelength!
There are stars and planets floating around me.
I don't think I can handle astronomy right now.
Astronomy's a lot easier to deal with than death, you moron!
So, suck it up and come to your senses already!
Double palm soul force!
Twist me!
Needles again?
No.
It's over now.
I hate to say it, but you're finished.
So much for round one.
It looks like I'll have some more experimenting to do.
What's happening to him?
He's going through soul rejection.
Your soul wavelength's reunited, but they're falling apart now.
I guess I found his limit.
Oh, well.
Soul protect.
Release.
It's another soul.
I don't know where it came from, but I can sense it.
I feel it, too.
It's a witch.
I've got a bitch.
We'll see you're in need.
I've got shit.
I can't see you in the village.
It's another wish.
Oh, I'm sad.
A witch, huh?
Yes, and one with a strong soul.
Very powerful.
My guess is she's the one who put that weapon inside the kid's body, too.
That's the witch's soul up there?
But how?
I should have felt a soul like that before now.
It's incredibly strong.
Soul protect.
What is that?
It's advanced magic.
Not all witches can use it.
The technique encloses the area around the soul with magic.
This blocks the soul's wavelength.
The witch is camouflaged, and her soul appears to be that of a normal human.
So that's the soul of a real witch?
Mama defeated something like that in order to turn Papa into a death site?
Pathetic.
Krona is such a weakling.
I'll have to punish him later.
Snake, snake, cobra, cobra.
But before I go, I'll punish you, too.
Won't that be fun?
Vector Arrows!
Let's go, soul residents!
Yes!
Witch hunter!
Quite impressive.
I just dropped by on a little errand.
Who would have thought I'd run into the DWMA's legendary Meister?
And Death Scythe, too.
What an unexpected pleasure.
I would love to stay and play with you kids a little longer.
But I'm afraid I can't.
Perhaps we can all play another time.
Hold it, lady!
No, it's okay.
Let's leave her for now.
I'm more worried about soul.
Soul.
Come on. Let's go home, Maka.
Interesting. Those two had a pretty rough time, it seems.
How is Sol holding up?
Stein is operating on him now.
He was hurt pretty bad, but I think he'll be all right.
The demon sword has surfaced, and it's united with a Meister,
actually embedded within him from what you say.
And behind it all is a powerful witch.
Goodness, it looks like things are getting pretty crazy around here, aren't they?
Oh, Lord Death, don't you think you might be taking this a little too lightly?
Oh?
How was your extra credit lesson?
All in all, it went pretty well, I guess.
Ugh, you're lucky. I have a remedial lesson tomorrow.
Personally, I'd rather have a remedial lesson.
Didn't you hear?
Apparently, a one-star kid named Soul Eater got injured and had to be brought back for surgery.
You're kidding. I hope he's all right.
What? Something happened to Soul?
Professor Stein?
Huh. Have you been waiting out here this whole time?
Why didn't you go take a nap or eat or something?
I need to know how Soul is!
The operation was a complete success.
Once he rests up a little bit, he'll be as good as new.
He's okay.
Thank you so much, Professor.
Um.
Hmm?
Would it be all right if I went in to check on him now?
Sure. That'll be fine.
Thank you.
That's a nice, fake smile you're wearing.
So tell me what you wouldn't tell Maka.
What is Soul's condition, really?
The wound itself is all right after surgery. That much I can say, at least.
But there is still something that bothers me.
Go on.
I'm not exactly certain, but it might be a curse.
A curse?
What kind of curse is it?
Will he be all right?
The demon sword, Ragnarok, has black blood.
Some of it appears to have gotten mixed into Soul's blood.
I can't say for sure how it will affect him, but I doubt it will be good.
Soul.
Back away. I won't let you touch my Meister.
I'm sorry.
I am your weapon partner, Maka.
That means I am always prepared to die for my Meister.
You did it all for me.
Just you wait.
I'm gonna become as strong as you are, Soul.
I promise I am.
Soul! Soul!
Are you okay?
It's going to be all right.
Blackstar is here for you now.
Open your eyes.
Let's look at my big, handsome face and you'll be cured for sure.
Blackstar, no!
Sorry about that, Maka.
Maka?
Oh, my goodness.
What happened to the door?
From the looks of it, things have been lively in here.
Dr. Medusa.
Good afternoon.
Hey, Doc, what's up?
Are you here to check on how Soul's doing?
Um, well, Miss Maka?
Yes.
What is it?
Can you do me a favor and help me out with your father?
I can't get him off my leg.
Oh, my darling.
My dear white-coated angel.
Please heal me.
My heart is in need of your sweet, sweet medical love.
But only you can kill me!
Soul had a difficult lesson, didn't he?
He was in pretty bad shape.
Yes, I'm sorry.
It's all my fault that he was hurt.
But he's okay now.
And as for you, this will only make you stronger, Maka.
Yeah.
クズ星 煌めく 夢の 欲しさ
I wanna be 行こうぜ 行こうぜ 行こうぜ 行こうぜ 行こうぜ
I want to be 行こうぜ quarter 行こうぜ
I want to be 行こうぜ 行こうぜ
e
I want to be